tradebanq.com 2015-05-19

# Privacy Policy - TradeBanq.com

1\. Our privacy policy describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect your personal information and it is important for you to review this privacy policy. 

By “personal information” we mean information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. 

2\. We do not consider anonymous information to constitute personal information as it cannot be used to identify a specific person. We collect personal information from you when you use TRADEBANQ.COM or its related websites and services (“Site”) 

By providing us with your personal information you expressly consent to us processing your personal information in accordance with the terms of our privacy policy. 

3\. We may amend our privacy policy at any time by posting a revised version on the Site. 

The revised version will be effective at the time we post it and, following such posting, your continued use of the Site will constitute your express consent to us continuing to process your personal information in accordance with the terms of our revised privacy policy.

Our privacy policy covers the following topics: 1. our collection of your personal information 2. our use of your personal information 3. accessing, reviewing and amending your personal information 4. third party website links 5. cookies 6. no spam or spoof emails 7. protecting your personal information 1. Our collection of your personal information a) As part of your registration on the Site, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, address, email address and/or telephone number and other similar information as well as other identifying information. 

b) Following your registration on the Site, you should not post any personal information (including any financial information) anywhere on the Site other than on the My Account section of the Site. 

Restricting the posting of personal information to the My Account section of the Site protects you from the possibility of fraud or identity theft. The posting by you of any personal information anywhere on the Site other than on the My Account section of the Site may lead to the suspension of your use of the Site.

c) Please note that we may use your Internet protocol (or IP) address (which is a unique number assigned to your computer server or your Internet service provider (or ISP)) to analyze user trends and improve the administration of the Site. We may also collect information about your computer (for example, browser type) and navigation information (for example, the pages you visit on the Site) along with the times that you access the Site. 

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. 

For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey. 

We may also collect feedback ratings and other comments relating to your use of the Site. 

Where we aggregate personal information for statistical purposes, such aggregated personal information shall be anonymous. 2. Our use of your personal information

a) We only use your personal information to provide services and customer support to you; to measure and improve our services to you; to prevent illegal activities and implement our user agreement with you (“User Agreement”); troubleshoot problems; provide you with promotional emails. 

b) Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose your personal information to law enforcement agencies, government agencies or other third parties where we are compelled so to do by court order or similar legal procedure; where we are required to disclose your personal information to comply with law; where we are cooperating with an ongoing law enforcement investigation or where we have a good faith belief that our disclosure of your personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate a possible violation of our User Agreement. 

c) In the event of a sale of TRADEBANQ.COM, any of its affiliates and subsidiaries or any related business assets, your personal information may be disclosed to any potential purchaser for the purposes of the continued provision of the Site or otherwise in relation to any such sale.

We may share your personal information with our other group companies so as to provide joint content and services to you, to help detect illegal acts and/or the violations of our policies. 

This contact information will be the personal information provided by you to us on registration and, as a result, should always be kept up-to-date. 

d) We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and will only share your personal information with third parties in accordance with this privacy policy. 

e) By registering on the Site, you give us your express consent to receive promotional emails about our services and emails announcing changes to, and new features on, the Site.

If, at any time, you decide that you do not wish to receive any such emails, you can opt out of receiving such emails by clicking on the link at the bottom of any of the emails or by going to the My Account section of the Site.

f) Additionally, we do use comments made by you about the Site for marketing purposes and by making such comments you expressly consent to our using such comments for marketing purposes.

3\. Accessing, reviewing and amending your personal information

a) You can access and review your personal information in the My Account section of the Site. 

If your personal information changes in any way or is incorrectly presented on the Site you should immediately update or correct your personal information (as applicable) by accessing the My Account section on the Site or, alternatively, by contacting our customer support team.

The “Customer Support” link at each Site webpage contains our customer support email and phone details.

b) Please note that we shall retain your personal information during and following the end of your use of the Site as required to comply with law, for technical troubleshooting requirements, to prevent fraud, to assist in any legal investigations and to take any other actions otherwise permitted by law.

4\. Third party website links The Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you when you leave the Site to read the privacy statements of each and every website you visit if you intend to provide personal information to that website. Our privacy policy applies solely to your personal information that we collect on the Site. 5. Cookies 

a) Like many websites, the Site uses 'cookie' technology (small computer files placed on your computer’s hard drive). When you go to particular website pages on the Site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. 

b) The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us improve your experience of the Site and also help us understand which parts of the Site are the most popular. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Site. 

6\. No spam or spoof emails We do not tolerate spam. To report Site related spam or spoof emails, please forward the email to LEGAL@ TRADEBANQ.COM . You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content. 7. Protecting your personal information

a) We hold your personal information on servers located in the United States.

By providing us with personal information, you consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and its storage on, our servers located in the United States. We take every precaution to safeguard all your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

All personal information is encrypted. However, the Internet is not a secure medium and we cannot guarantee the privacy of your personal information. 

b) You must enter your username and password each time you want to access your account. 

c) Choose your password carefully using unique numbers, letters and special characters. 

Never share your username and password with anyone. 

If you are concerned that your username or password has been compromised, please contact our customer support team immediately and ensure you change your password by logging onto the My Account section of the Site. 

8\. How you can contact us about privacy questions If you have questions or concerns about our collection and use of your personal information, please contact our customer support team at the “Customer Support” link on any Site webpage.
